atproperties.com 2016-10-11

# Privacy Policy | @properties

#### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name,e-mail address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

#### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason what so ever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

#### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systemsto recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website,conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriateto comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, orsafety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other partiesfor marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. None the less,we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

#### Contact Us

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy, or if you wish to update the personal information you have provided to us, you may do so by contacting us here.

#### Updates and Effective Date

We reserve the right to make changes to our Privacy Policy from time to time for any reason.Such changes, modifications, additions or deletions shall be effective immediately upon posting, unless otherwise indicated. We have no duty or obligation to inform prior visitors that changes have been made, regardless of the scope and importance of the changes. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this Privacy Policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it and to whom we disclose it. Your continued use of the Site after such changes are posted will be deemed to constitute your agreement to and acceptance of such changes.
